{
    "subject": "resource/Rokunin_no_ansatsusha",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/Nikkatsu",
    "human_readable": "Rokunin no ansatsu-sha was produced by Nikkatsu.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9623651504516602,
            "question": "Who produced Rokunin no ansatsu-sha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9200505614280701,
            "question": "What production company made Rokunin no ansatsu-sha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8308929800987244,
            "question": "When was Rokunin no ansatsu-sha probably released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8067619800567627,
            "question": "Is Rokunin no ansatsu-sha a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7318335175514221,
            "question": "Name a movie produced by Nikkatsu."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6106239557266235,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Rokunin no ansatsu-sha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6012589335441589,
            "question": "What other movies did Nikkatsu produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6000949740409851,
            "question": "What genre is Rokunin no ansatsu-sha likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5907395482063293,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in Rokunin no ansatsu-sha?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5195014476776123,
            "question": "What is Nikkatsu known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rokunin no ansatsu-sha was produced by Nikkatsu.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4235_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in Rokunin no ansatsu-sha?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4235_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Rokunin no ansatsu-sha likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4235_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other movies did Nikkatsu produce?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4235_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4235_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4235_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4235_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4235_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4235_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4235_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4235_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4235_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4235_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4235_44.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "no \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "**Rewrite**: The production of Rokunin no ansatsu-sha, a film, was indeed carried out by the renowned Japanese film studio Nikkatsu."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not contain any information about the production company of the film \"Rokunin no Ansatsusha\". Therefore, we cannot confirm or deny that it was produced by Nikkatsu based on the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n       \"output\": \"yes\"\n    }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Nikkatsu as the production company for Rokunin no Ansatsusha in the provided text.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Nikkatsu being involved in the production of Rokunin no Ansatsusha.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided about a production company for Rokunin no Ansatsusha in the given context.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}